Finding Aid of the Society of American Archivists Records, 1935-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1935-2016, UWM Manuscript Collection 172; 271.9 cubic ft. (385 boxes, including 16 audio cassettes and 33 videocassettes) 1 oversize folder 7,545 digital files (26.2 GB) 1 film reel 5 microfilm reels approximately 170 books and serial titles
  - 3. Secretary, 1936-1976, 200/03
    - 1. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1936-1956, 200/03/01; 3.4 cubic ft. (4 boxes)
      - Phillip C. Brooks, 1936-1942
        - Correspondence Regarding American Archivist, 1936-1941 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence Regarding News Notes in American Archivist, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 30)
        - Correspondence Regarding Reviews in American Archivist, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 34)
        - Correspondence Regarding Editorial Board, 1937-1941 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        - Correspondence Regarding Postal Matters (Second Class Mailing Permit), 1938-1942 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        - Correspondence with American Archivist Editor Regarding Index/Title Page, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        - Correspondence with Banta Company, 1938-1941 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence with Council Member Connor, 1938-1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence with Council Member Norton, 1937-1942 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence with Editor Pease, 1937-1942 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
        - Correspondence with President Connor, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence with President Leland, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence with President Newsome, 1936-1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence with Vice Presidents, 1937-1941 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - Council, Meetings, 1936-1942 (Box 2, Folder 35)
        - Historical Background Material, 1935-1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - Preservation of Local Archives, 1932, 1939-1942, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 32)
        - Printing and Duplicating, 1939-1942 (Box 2, Folder 33)
        - Reports of the Secretary, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - Social Science Research Council, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Southern Historical Association, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - Special Libraries Association, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Lester J. Cappon, 1942-1950
        - AASLH, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - American Archivist
          - Correspondence Regarding, 1941-1951 (Box 3, Folder 20)
          - Correspondence Regarding Advertising, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
          - Correspondence Regarding Exchanges for, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 27)
          - Correspondence Regarding News Notes in, 1942-1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
          - Correspondence Regarding Reviews in, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 31)
          - Correspondence Regarding Selection of Editor, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 29)
        - American Archivist Editor
          - Correspondence, 1942-1949 (Box 3, Folder 21)
          - Correspondence with Pease, Norton and Trever, 1944-1949 (Box 3, Folder 22-24)
          - Correspondence with Regarding Index, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 28)
        - American Documentation Institute, 1937-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - Annual Business Meeting, Minutes, 1943, 1947, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 35)
        - Banta Company, Correspondence with, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 25)
        - British Records Association, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - Certificate of Incorporation, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, A-J, 1942-1950 (Box 4, Folder 7-10)
        - Correspondence, K-Z, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 11-14)
        - Correspondence with Council Members, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
        - Correspondence with Council Member Brooks, 1942-1947 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence with President Brooks, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence with President Buck, 1945-1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence with President Connor, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence with President Crittenden, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence with President Norton, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence with Vice Presidents, 1945-1947 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - Council, 1943-1950 (Box 3, Folder 34)
        - Editorial Policy, Correspondence Regarding Criticism of, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 26)
        - National Records Management Council, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - National Research Council, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - National Society of Autograph Collectors, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - Torch Press, Correspondence with, 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 32)
        - United Nations Economic and Social Council, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Roger Thomas
        - American Archivist, Correspondence with Editor of, 1950-1953 (Box 3, Folder 33)
        - Annual Business Meeting, Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 37)
        - Council, Meetings, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 36)
        - Correspondence with Council Members, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence with President Brooks, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence with President McCain, 1950-1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
        - General Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - United Nations Economic and Social Council, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Henry E. Edmunds, 1953-1955
        - Secretary's Report, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Henry Browne
        - Committees, 1955-1956; Miscellaneous Records, 1955-1956; SAA Leaflet, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Council, Meetings, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 38)
        - Council Members, Correspondence with, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        - General Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Three-Year Plan for the Financing of a Full-Time Secretariat, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - 2. Committee Files, 1936-1962, 200/03/02; 5 cubic ft. (5 boxes)
      - Background and Development of Committees, 1936-1956 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Archival Bibliography, 1942-1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Auditing, 1937-1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Audio Visual, 1951-1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Buildings and Equipment (Archival Buildings and Filing Equipment), 1940-1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Business Archives, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Business Records (Institutional Archives), 1937-1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Business Records: Survey, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Church Records, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Civil Defense (Microfilm Contributions Program), 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Classification and Cataloging, 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - College and University Archives, 1948-1953 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
      - Confederate Records, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Conservation of Cultural Resources, 1941-1944 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Constitution Revision, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Cooperation, 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Emergencies, Collection and Preservation of Materials for the History of, 1940-1944 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Emergency Activities, 1950-1952 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Emergency Agencies, History and Organization of Government, 1940-1944 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Emergency Transfer and Storage of Archives, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Historical Manuscripts, Joint ASSLH-SAA Committee on, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Historical Records Survey, 1937-1942 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - ICA, 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - International Relations, 1936-1957 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
      - Labor Archives and Records, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Legislation, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - [National Archives] Library, 1938-1942 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Maps and Charts, 1936-1942 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Membership
        - Founding Members, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - General, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - History and Policy, 1949-1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        - Reports, 1942-1957 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        - Areas, 1946-1955 (Box 2, Folder 30)
        - Areas 1-4, 1947-1955 (Box 2, Folder 31-34)
        - Areas 5-13, 1947-1955 (Box 3, Folder 1-9)
        - Directory, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence, Directory, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous Lists and Records, 1950-1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - Directory and Related Material, 1953-1957 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - Notification of Membership Changes, 1954-1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Membership, 1937-1955 (Box 2, Folder 25-29)
      - Membership, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Microcard Project, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Microfilming, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Microphotography, Secretary's Correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Motion Pictures, 1936-1939 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - NHPRC, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Negro Archives, American Council of Learned Societies, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Nominations, General, 1939-1953, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Nominations, 1936-1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Nominations, W.D. Overman Files, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Nominations, 1948-1952 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Photographic Techniques, 1945-1956 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Preservation Methods, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Professional Standards, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Program, 1937-1941 (Box 3, Folder 31-35)
      - Program, 1942-1944, 1951, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 1-6)
      - Pronunciation, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Protection of Archives Against Hazards of War, 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Public Relations, 1936-1943 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Publication Policy of Archival Agencies, 1936-1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Publicity, 1943-1958 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Records Management, 1936-1947 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Records Management
        - Reports, 1937-1957 (Box 4, Folder 13)
        - Draft of "Public Records Management" Pamphlet, 1944-1949 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Records Management, 1947-1952, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
      - Reduction of Archival Material, Report on European Policies, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Research, 1942-1948 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Resolutions, 1941-1958 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Scientific and Specialized Personnel, National Roster, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - State and Local Records, 1941-1955 (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
      - State and Local Records
        - Comparative Study of State and U.S. Territorial Laws Governing Archives, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 23)
        - Archival, Historical and Museum Activities in Georgia on State/Local Level, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - Reports, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Comparative Study of State and U.S. Territorial Laws Governing Archives, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - State Archives, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
      - State Archives
        - Directory, 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - Directory Data, 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - Legislation, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        - Microfilm Survey, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 9)
        - Records Destruction Survey, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 10)
        - Salary Survey, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 11)
        - State Uniform Public Records Law, Chair's Correspondence Regarding, 1938-1940 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
        - Uniform Legislation Commission Correspondence and Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 5, Folder 14)
        - Uniform Legislation Committee, Draft of Uniform Act, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - State Records
        - Alabama History and Archives Building, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 16)
        - Promotion, 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 17)
        - Reports, Surveys and Correspondence, 1942-1957 (Box 5, Folder 18)
        - Directory, List of Members, 1938-1947 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - State Records, 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Terminology, 1936-1942 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Training of Archivists, 1937-1946 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Training of Archivists, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 3. Dolores C. Renze, 1941-1966, 200/03/03
      - 1. Reading File (Outgoing Correspondence), 1956-1964, 200/03/03/01; 1 cubic ft. (1 box)
        - 1956 October 1-1957 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - 1957 October 1-1958 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - 1958 October 1-1959 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        - 1959 October 1-1960 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        - 1960 October 1-1961 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - 1961 October 1-1962 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - 1962- October 1-1963 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - 1963 May 1-1964 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 2. Committee Files, 1955-1966, 200/03/03/02; 3.2 cubic ft. (4 boxes)
        - Archives Manual, 1955-1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - Archives of the Professions, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 13)
        - Audio Visual, 1957-1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - Auditing, 1956-1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Bibliography (Archival), 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Buildings and Equipment, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - Buildings and Equipment, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        - Business Records, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
        - Business Records, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
        - Church Records, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
        - Civil War Centennial, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Civil War Centennial, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 18)
        - College and University Archives, 1958-1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - College and University Archives, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 19)
        - Committee Chair Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Federal and State Relations, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - Finance, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 20)
        - General, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - General, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
        - Gondos Memorial Award, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - Historical Manuscripts [Joint ASSLH-SAA Committee on Historical Manuscripts], 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - International Relations, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - International Relations, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
        - Labor Records, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
        - Labor Union Records, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - Local Arrangements, 1957-1958, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 15-18)
        - Local Arrangements, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 23)
        - Long-Range Planning, 1948-1952, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - Long-Range Planning, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 24)
        - Long-Range Planning, Foundation Plan, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        - Manuscripts [Joint ASSLH-SAA Committee on Historical Manuscripts], 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - Manuscripts [Joint ASSLH-SAA Committee on Historical Manuscripts], 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 25)
        - Membership, 1957-1961 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
        - Membership
          - Chair's Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
          - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        - Memorial Fund, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 26)
        - Microfilming, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        - Microfilming, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
        - Microfilming
          - Chair's Correspondence, 1956-1959; Microfilm Questionnaire, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
          - Correspondence of Dorothy Taylor, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        - Municipal Records, 1957-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
        - New Mexico Public Records Act (Special Area and Ad Hoc Committee), 1959 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        - Nominations, 1957-1962 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
        - Nominations, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 28)
        - Nominations, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
          Restricted. Requires permission of executive committee to access.
        - Preservation, 1957-1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - Professional Standards (Includes Fellows), 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - Professional Standards, Fellows, 1957-1960 (Box 3, Folder 6-8)
        - Program, 1957-1962 (Box 3, Folder 9-15)
        - Program, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 29)
        - Publicity, 1955-1962 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        - Publicity, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 30)
        - Records Management, 1957-1965 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
        - Records Management, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 31)
        - Resolutions, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 19)
        - Resolutions, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 32)
        - Revenue, Report by Leon deValinger, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
        - Science Manuscripts and Archives, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 33)
        - Standards [Joint AASLH-SAA Committee to Formulate Standards by Which Local Depositories Might Qualify as Federal Records Depositories], 1950-1953 (Box 3, Folder 21)
        - State and Local Records
          - Archival Documentation or Administrative Improvement & Development Award, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 35)
          - Correspondence Regarding Handbook, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 26)
          - Directory of State & Provincial Archivists & Records Administrators, 1961, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
          - Handbook of State & Provincial Archivists & Records Administrators, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
          - Handbook Photographs, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 28)
          - Handbook, Manuscript Draft, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 27)
          - Municipal Records, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
          - Records Management Function Survey in States, 1960, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 29)
        - State Archives, Comparative Study of State and U.S. Territorial Laws Governing Archives, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
        - State Records, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
        - State Records, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        - State Records, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 34)
        - State Records
          - Correspondence Regarding State Libraries, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 1)
          - Guide to State and Provincial Archival Agencies, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
          - Microfilm Project, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 9)
          - Microphotography Reports on Record Display, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 38)
          - Orders and Correspondence Regarding Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - Waldo Gifford Leland Prize, 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        - Workshops, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
      - 3. General Files, 1941-1972, 200/03/03/03; 5.4 cubic ft. (6 boxes)
        - Adams Institute of Marketing, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Advisory Services, Declaration of Policy Relating to, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - AHA, Luncheon Program, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
        - ALA, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - American Archivist
          - Advertising Editor, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
          - Allen Press, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
          - Bids for Publishing, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
          - Contract-Subscription Agencies, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
          - Editor Munden, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
          - Index (Contract), 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
          - Indexing by Karl Trever, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 5)
          - Microfilm Copies of, 1955-1960, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
          - Postal Rates and POD Form 3526, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - Prospectus, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 11)
          - Torch Press, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
          - University Microfilm, Inc., Contract and Orders, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
        - Annual Meeting, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        - Annual Meeting, Program, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 13)
        - Archives of Learned Societies, Walter G. Leland Proposal, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 15)
        - Asia Foundation, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 16)
        - Constitution and Amendments: Corresponding Working Papers, 1936-1961 (Box 4, Folder 17)
        - Council and Officers, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 20)
        - Council and Officers
          - Archives "Opportunities" Brochures, Council Correspondence Regarding, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 19)
          - Council Meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 21-27)
          - Vice President Alldredge, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 28)
        - Council on Library Resources, SAA Grants, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 29)
        - Deaths of Members, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 30)
        - Decatur House (Meeting of Representatives of Cultural Groups), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Directory, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 31)
        - Education and Training
          - American University Institute, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
          - Institutes, 1956-1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
          - Requests for Educational Guidance, 1958-1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - Fellows [First Elected Class], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - Fellows, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - Fellows, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - Fellows, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 32)
        - Fellows, Historical Background and Development, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Fellows, Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - First International Congress of Reprography, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 33)
        - Forms, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 34)
        - Honorary Membership, 1941-1960 (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Honorary Membership, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 35)
        - Internal Revenue Service, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 36)
        - International Conference of the Roundtable of Archives, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 37)
        - International Conference of the Roundtable on Archives, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - International Cooperation Administration, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 33)
        - Latin American Guide to Historical Sources, Rockefeller Foundation Grant Proposal, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 38)
        - Legislation: General, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
        - Librarian-Archivist, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
        - Life Members and Fund, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 39)
        - Louisiana State Archives, Firing of State Archivist, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - Mailing List Use, 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 40)
        - Membership
          - Biographical Data
            - A-Z, 1956-1962 (Box 6, Folder 1-2, 4, 6-10)
            - President Leon de Valinger, Jr., 1956-1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
            - Wayne C. Grover, 1956-1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
          - Biographical Data for Directory, A-Z, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 10)
          - Biographical Questionnaire and Renze's Retirement as Secretary, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 4)
          - Biographical Survey
            - A-Z, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 5-8)
            - Canada, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
            - Deceased Since 1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
            - Foreign, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
            - Institutional or Subscribers, No Response, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
            - No Response or Unwilling, US Only, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Directories, 1957, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Directory, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - Directory, Correspondence Regarding, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 3)
          - Mailing Lists, 1957-1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
          - Members and Subscribers, circa 1940-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
          - Miscellaneous, Lists, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 15-17)
          - Recent Changes, Deletion, New Members, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - Minutes and Reports of Council Meetings and Annual Business Meetings, 1955-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - National Fire Protection Association, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 41)
        - Non-Profit Corporation Studies, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 37)
        - Office of Civil and Defense Mobilization, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - Officers and Chairmen, Lists of, 1937-1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        - Official SAA Seal and Motto, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - Organizations
          - AASLH, 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 42)
          - AHA, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 46)
          - ALA, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 47)